

Mani Meskartehrani

☐ Gmail ((778) 361- 0725 Vancouver,BC,CA LinkedIn





PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Motivated and driven digital marketing specialist with over 5 years of experience in the IT industry and SEO. Self-starting, enthusiastic SEO specialist with solid knowledge of technical SEO and on-page SEO, and skilled in website analysis, keyword research, and strategic planning. Currently, I am pursuing the Digital Marketing Institute Professional certificate to expand my knowledge.

SUMMARY OF SKILLS

- Working experience with the most well-known CMS such as WordPress.
- Experienced with programming languages and knowledge such as HTML/CSS, JavaScript, and PHP.
- Familiar with website architecture and UX/UI best practices for SEO.
- SEO schedule for content writing and monitoring the performance.

Key Skills

- HTML/CSS
- JavaScript
- PHP / CMS
- Technical SEO
- SEO keyword research
- On page SEO
- · Competitor analysis
- A/B testing
- SEO web content analysis
- Link building

WORK HISTORY

Digital Marketing Specialist (SEO Specialist) | Internship

Oct 2021 – Jan 2022

Vancoweb (Digital Marketing Agency) | Hastings, BC

- · Conduct keyword research, analysis, and technical optimization using SEMrush, Moz, Ahrefs, Google keyword planner, Google search console.
- Developed a strategic plan for SEO audits and resolving technical SEO issues.

Website Analytics Specialist (Technical SEO)

Jun 2016 - Jan 2020

IPM-IRNIC | Tehran, Iran

- Performed in-depth web analysis to discover technical SEO issues and created an optimization plan to resolve them with the technical team, which resulted in 21% increasing traffic.
- Solved website technical SEO issues to improve ranking.

Web Developer | Volunteer

Jun 2012 – Jan 2015

Kaj Real Estate | Tehran, Iran

• Designed and developed Front-end and Back-end of the store's website using HTML5/CSS3/PHP technology

EDUCATION

Master of Business Administration | Digital Marketing

Oct 2020 - Jan 2022

University of Canada West – BC, CA

Bachelor of Engineering | Software University of Guilan - Rasht, Iran

Sep 2007 – July 2012